webtransfer.com 2015-03-28

# WebTransfer | Money transfer, Online payments

Dated: 24 August 2014, London, UK

Protecting your data and financial details is very important to Webtransfer.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by Webtransfer.

**Information we may collect about you**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information that you provide by filling in forms on the webtransfer.com website. This includes information you provide at the time of registering (such as contact information, social security number, copies of identification documents or documents verifying identification from publically accessible databases) or carrying out a transaction on the webtransfer.com website;

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;

Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfillment of your orders;

Details of your visits to our site.

We will hold the above information for as long as is necessary in order to provide you with the Webtransfer service, deal with any specific issues that you may raise or otherwise as is required by law or any relevant regulatory body.

**IP Addresses**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical information about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

**Cookies**

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users to our site. This helps us provide you with a good experience when you browse our site and also allows us to improve our site. Please note that it is possible to disable cookies being stored on your computer by changing your browser settings. However, this site may not perform properly or some features may not be available to you if you disable cookies.

**Where we store your personal information**

The data we collect from you is stored in the UK but may be transferred to and stored at a destination outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside of the EEA. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing.

Your passwords are stored on Webtransfer servers in encrypted form. We do not disclose your account details, postal or email addresses to anyone except when legally required to do so. We do disclose your first name and the first letter of your last name to other members, who are transacting with you.

Sensitive information between your browser and the webtransfer.com website is transferred in encrypted form using Secure Socket Layer (SSL). When transmitting sensitive information, you should always make sure that your browser can validate the Webtransfer.com certificate.

It is your responsibility to keep your password secure. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although Webtransfer will do its best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site, any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try and prevent any unauthorized access.

**How we use your information**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

-     provide you with our services and to carry out any transactions that you request

-     ensure the content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and your computer or mobile device

-     notify you about changes to our services

**Disclosure of your information**

We may disclose your first and last name information to the user you are trying to make a transaction with.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

- in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets;

- if Webtransfer or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party; or

- if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection.

**Your rights**

You have the right to ask us not to share your personal data by contacting us at [privacy@webtransfer.com](mailto:privacy@webtransfer.com)

The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access information held about you by submitting a request in accordance with the act and is subject to a £10 administrative fee. All such requests should be sent to privacy@webtransfer.com.

**Changes to this policy**

Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page, and where appropriate, notified to you by email.

**Contact**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcome and should be addressed to privacy@webtransfer.com.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

The www.webtransfer.com site may contain links to other web sites. As such, Webtransfer is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting a notice of the change (or an amended Privacy Policy) on our web site at www.webtransfer.com

**Questions or Comments**

If you would like more information regarding this Privacy Policy or you believe that the information we have on file about you is inaccurate or incomplete, you can call us at the number on the back of your card or contact us at +44 203 290 9691.
